Friday night bailout packs Matching skirts and bubble attacks Shots lined up like a firing squad Screaming, woo!
Like it's a gift from God Selfie sticks and broken heels Twerking to songs they don't even feel Hair extensions, vulva fry Echoes like a battle cry Woo girls, break the sound Every bar becomes battleground Raise your glass and raise your bitch Every... another glitch
In the matrix of your brain, guessables of drunk disdain.
Blue girl, three for fame, but no one here remembers your name.
One just cried, no one knows why.
Another's making out with some finance guy.
They laugh at me, it's from 2012.
And college slay, just kill me now.
Shots for brunch and brunch for clout.
Mortnags now scream and shout, birthday sashes, glitter bombs, monthlesses mixed with photobombs.
Woo girls, break the sound, every bar becomes battleground.
Raise a glass and raise your pitch, every another glitch.
In the logic of the night, every cheer just chills the vibe.
Woo girls, dance and scream like chaos in a forever 21 dream.
Loom in my hair, swoop up in my shades.
Oop, the left eye just tap in me up, and bash that neck around your sweet boy.
Blue girls, queens are cringe, makes my eardrums singe.
Fart out from attention short, I'll ride in a jukebox court.
Blue girls, go full send, till the hangover makes amends.
Rude girls, you rule the scene, with a scream that haunts my mongrel dreams.